<?xml version="1.0"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="http://www.insomniacmania.com/site-editor/rss-news-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><title>Insomniac Mania</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com</link><description>The movie site that never sleeps</description><language>en-us</language><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 10:02:56 +0000</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 10:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><generator>Fusion Robot</generator><managingEditor>info@insomniacmania.com (Rob Shan Lone)</managingEditor><webMaster>info@insomniacmania.com (Rob Shan Lone)</webMaster><ttl>5</ttl><item><title>Wolverine is soft according to Hugh Jackman?!</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3816</link><description>The Wolverine spin off is really underway. Hugh Jackman returns as Logan in the X-Men spinoff.USA Today has published six new photos of Wolverine. Jackman claimed he is &quot;not mad about&quot; the character. He believes he has gone &quot;soft&quot; and thought the films had gone &quot;away from the essence of who Wolverine really is.&quot;In an abstract way, Jackman believes the character is a lot like &quot;Dirty Harry or Han Solo.&quot;Check out the pictures, Coming Soon and our forum for more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3816</guid></item><item><title>Wolverine trailer on MTV</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3815</link><description>A trailer for Wolverine is now out at MTV. The feature is set for a May 1st release. Directed by Gavin Hood, the prequel stars Hugh Jackman, Liev Schreiber, Ryan Reynolds, Taylor Kitsch, Will.i.am, Danny Huston, Dominic Monaghan, Daniel Henney and Lynn Collins.For more information check out our forum and Coming Soon.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3815</guid></item><item><title>Four new featurettes for Watchmen</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3802</link><description>There are four new featurettes &quot;Watchmen&quot;!Directed by Zack
Snyder, the superhero film follows a group of former vigilantes as
tensions heighten between the United States and the Soviet Union. Thank you coming soon. Watch one, two, three and four now.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3802</guid></item><item><title>Beezus and Ramona to star Ginnifer Goodwin, John Corbett and Bridget Moynahan</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3814</link><description>A film based on the classic children's book series &quot;Beezus and Ramona&quot;
is in the works. The book written by Beverly Cleary is likely to star
Ginnifer Goodwin, John Corbett and Bridget Moynahan.

Director Elizabeth Allen is to helm the project with Denise Di Novi and
Alison Greenspan producing. Goodwin will play Aunt Bea, and Moynahan
and Corbett will play the two girls' parents, Dorothy and Bob Quimby.
Shooting is scheduled to start in Vancouver in April. For more information check out The Hollywood Reporter and our forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3814</guid></item><item><title>Sucker Punch to star Amanda Seyfried, Vanessa Hudgens, Abbie Cornish, Evan Rachel Wood and Emma Stone</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3813</link><description>Zack Snyder is directing an all-female cast for his next feature, &quot;Sucker Punch&quot;.Set in the 1950s, the action fantasy follows a girl, Babydoll,&amp;nbsp; who is confined to a mental institution by her stepfather. He intends to have her lobotomized in five days. While there, she imagines an alternative reality to hide her from the pain, and in that world, she begins planning her escape, needing to steal five objects to help get her out before she is deflowered by a vile man.Snyder co-wrote the script with Steve Shibuya. The feature is described as an 'Alice in Wonderland' with machine guns with the inclusion of dragons, B-52 bombers and brothels.The feature is likely to star Vanessa Hudgens, Abbie Cornish, Evan Rachel Wood and Emma Stone. Amanda Seyfried is in talks to topline. The rest of the cast would play inmates who also fall into the alternate reality adventure.Hudgens would play a character named Blondie, Cornish would play Sweet Pea, Wood would play Rocket and Stone would play Amber. The Hollywood Reporter hosts more information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3813</guid></item><item><title>Character montages for The Watchmen starting with Dr. Manhattan</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3806</link><description>Character montages have started to appear on NBC. We kickstart with Dr. Manhattan! Stay tuned because five more montages are set for release over the next few days.Directed by Zack Snyder, the comic feature stars Malin Akerman, Billy Crudup, Matthew Goode, Carla Gugino, Jackie Earle Haley, Jeffrey Dean Morgan and Patrick Wilson. Opens in conventional and IMAX theaters on March 6th.Thank Coming Soon for this update. For more excitement join our rebellion in the forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3806</guid></item><item><title>Fathom to star Megan Fox</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3812</link><description>Megan Fox is attached to &quot;Fathom&quot; a comic book based underwater adventure.Developed by the recently deceased comic artist Michael Turner; the series follows a young woman named Aspen who learns she is a member of a race of aquatic humanoids who possess the ability to control water.Jordan Mechner, the creator of video game &quot;Prince of Persia&quot;, is penning the script. Megan Fox, Peter Safran, Frank Mastromauro, Steve Bessen and Brian Austin Green are producing.Turner will be credited as executive producer. For more information check out The Hollywood Reporter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3812</guid></item><item><title>Jonah Hex to star Josh Brolin, John Malkovich and Megan Fox</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3811</link><description>Josh Brolin, John Malkovich and Megan Fox are set to star in the DC comics action Western adaptation of &quot;Jonah Hex&quot;. Fox will portray Leila, a gun-wielding beauty and love interest of Hex (Brolin), a scarred bounty hunter tracking a voodoo practitioner (Malkovich) who wants to raise an army of undead to liberate the South.Shooting will commence in April with Jimmy Hayward set to direct. Andrew Lazar and Akiva Goldsman are producing. The Hollywood Reporter has more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3811</guid></item><item><title>H2 by Rob Zombie - the next Halloween sequel</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3810</link><description>Rob Zombie's &quot;H2&quot; has more photographs up at ShockTillYouDrop.com. The Halloween sequel stars Scout Taylor-Compton, Mane, Danielle Harris, Daniel Roebuck, Ezra Buzzington, Mark Christopher Lawrence, Jeffrey Daniel Phillips, Dayton Callie, Richard Brake, Matt Bush and Howard Hesseman.The feature is set for release on August 28th. The last photograph apparently contains a spoiler of Michael Myers. For more information check out Comingsoon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3810</guid></item><item><title>Inception the sci-fi action thriller with Leonardo DiCaprio</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3809</link><description>Leonardo DiCaprio is set for the sci-fi action thriller, &quot;Inception&quot;.Director Christopher Nolan will helm the project for Warner Bros. Pictures. Nolan will be directing from his own script; the project is described as a contemporary sci-fi action movie set within &quot;the architecture of the mind.&quot;The shoot is set to start this summer for a 2010 release.Chris Thomas and Emma Thomas are producing. The Hollywood Reporter has more; check out our forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3809</guid></item><item><title>The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader comes out in 2010</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3807</link><description>According to Variety we will have to wait till December 10th 2010 for the release of &quot;The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader&quot;Twentieth Century Fox and Walden Media recently partnered on the &quot;Narnia&quot; film series after Disney and Walden split up.It is the first film to have a release in 2010.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3807</guid></item><item><title>Scandal Makers helmed by Barry Sonnenfeld</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3805</link><description>Director Barry Sonnenfeld will helm a remake of the Korean feature, &quot;Scandal Makers&quot;.Revolving around a pop singer whose life is turned upside-down when he discovers that he has a daughter and a grandson.A producer has yet to be found for the project. Variety and our forum has more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3805</guid></item><item><title>A debut trailer for Terminator Salvation</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3804</link><description>A debut trailer for Terminator Salvation is now up thanks to Yahoo! Movies. In 2018, John Connor is to lead the human resistance against Skynet. Future Connor must decide if Marcus Wright (Sam Worthington), a stranger whose last memory is of being on death row, is from the future, or has been rescued from the past.The uncover the terrible secret behind the operation. Exploding on theaters May 21st.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3804</guid></item><item><title>Dead of Night to star Sam Huntington and Brandon Routh</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3808</link><description>Director Kevin Munroe is to helm the Italian comic book adaptation &quot;Dead of Night&quot;. Sam Huntington and Brandon Routh are set to star in the feature.Routh portrays the reluctant private investigator, Dylan Dog, who is drawn into the world of vampires, werewolves and the undead. Huntington will star as Marcus, sidekick to Routh's character.The film started shooting last week. For more information check out IESB.net and our forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3808</guid></item><item><title>New Posters for Terminator Salvation</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3798</link><description>Christian Bale, Sam Worthington, Anton Yelchin, Bryce Dallas Howard, Moon Bloodgood and Common star in &quot;Terminator Salvation&quot;.Yahoo! Movies is hosting trailers and new posters and photos from McG's new film. The feature is set for a May 21st release.Join our forum for more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3798</guid></item><item><title>Never Let Me Go with Keira Knightley, Andrew Garfield and Carey Mulligan</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3799</link><description>Mark Romanek will direct the upcoming sci-fi thriller, &quot;Never Let Me Go.&quot; Keira Knightley, Andrew Garfield and Carey Mulligan will star in the feature, which will revolve around cloning!Andrew Macdonald and Allon Reich are producing from a screenplay written by Alex Garland. Shooting will commence in April through out locations in England. Variety has more, as does our forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3799</guid></item><item><title>Up in the Air for George Clooney and Jason Bateman</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3800</link><description>Jason Reitman is directing an adaptation of the Walter Kirn novel &quot;Up in the Air&quot;. George Clooney and Jason Bateman are set to star in the feature. Clooney portrays a corporate downsizer who is obsessed with collecting frequent flyer miles at the expense of having a life. Bateman will play his boss. Variety hosts more information, as does our forum; check it out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3800</guid></item><item><title>Baster with Jennifer Aniston and Jason Bateman</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3801</link><description>Jennifer Aniston and Jason Bateman are set to star in the comedy &quot;Baster.&quot;Shooting will start later this month after Bateman has finished filming &quot;Up in the Air.&quot; Variety and our forum has more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3801</guid></item><item><title>Rape will star Maria Bello, Abigail Breslin and Samuel L. Jackson</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3803</link><description>Harold Becker is to direct &quot;Rape&quot;. An indie drama which will star Maria Bello, Abigail Breslin and Samuel L. Jackson. Michael Mendelsohn is producing.The plot centers on a mother (Bello) recovering from a brutal gang rape who is stalked by the perpetrators but is protected by a sympathetic cop (Jackson). Breslin will play the woman's 12-year-old daughter, who witnesses the attack.The feature is based on the Joyce Carol Oates novella published in 2003. TV writer John Mankiewicz has adapted the screenplay. Join our forum to talk about this feature. Variety holds more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3803</guid></item><item><title>A contemporary version of Total Recall is in the works with Neal H. Moritz to helm</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3797</link><description>A contemporary version of &quot;Total Recall&quot; is in the works?! Based on the Philip K. Dick story &quot;We Can Remember It for You Wholesale&quot;; the plot revolves around a man who is haunted by a recurring dream of journeying to Mars who buys a literal dream vacation from a company called Rekall Inc., which sells implanted memories.Neal H. Moritz will helm this new feature with the hopes that the recent advancements in technology can help tell the &quot;Recall&quot; story in a fresh way.We are big fans of the original film, so much so we are dedicating time to a new design revolving around Quaid. Look out for our book &quot;You think this is the real Quaid.&quot; Whilst we don't feel the film needs a revamp it may be interesting to explore the works of Philip. K Dick from another angle.The Hollywood Reporter has more information as does our forum.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3797</guid></item><item><title>Adventureland by Greg Mottola</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3796</link><description>Greg Mottola's &quot;Adventureland&quot; has a new trailer! Jesse Eisenberg, Ryan Reynolds, Kristen Stewart, Martin Starr, Paige Howard, Kristen Wiig and Bill Hader star in the R-rated comedy.This feature is expected to come out on March 27th.For more information check out Coming Soon and IGN.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3796</guid></item><item><title>Samuel L. Jackson is Nick Fury</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3795</link><description>Samuel L. Jackson is making the deal to portray Nick Fury in Iron Man 2. The character is the leader of the espionage unit S.H.I.E.L.D.Jackson is likely to see his likeness on future toys that come with the Happy Meals, for this is a long-term deal. We are talking like 9 potential occurances in future comic films! Expect to be bombarded with The First Avenger: Captain America, Thor, The Avengers, S.H.I.E.L.D. and other potential seqels.If you stayed till the end of Iron Man, you would have seen Jackson portray Fury for the first time as he asked Robert Downey Jr.'s Tony Stark to join his group. For more information check out The Hollywood Reporter and Variety.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3795</guid></item><item><title>Quartermain scriped by Mark Verheiden</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3794</link><description>A science fiction adventure called &quot;Quartermain&quot; is in the works for DreamWorks. Penned by Mark Verheiden, no details have yet been released on the project, except that it springs from an original idea.Verheiden has his hands in many pots, not only is he a writer and producer on TV's &quot;Heroes&quot; and &quot;Battlestar Galactica&quot;, he also has an adaptation of Teen Titans in development at Warner Bros. and Ark, based on his comic, in development at Columbia. The Hollywood Reporter has more information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3794</guid></item><item><title>Terminator Salvation on the cover of Empire magazine </title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3793</link><description>An amazing cover has been published on the latest edition of Empire magazine. The cover features Christian Bale as John Connor in Terminator Salvation.Christian Bale, Sam Worthington, Anton Yelchin, Bryce Dallas Howard, Moon Bloodgood and Common star. McG directed this picture.It all kicks off on May 21st so for more information check out our forum and Coming Soon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3793</guid></item><item><title>Yogi Bear to be a CG</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3792</link><description>&quot;Yogi Bear&quot; will be director by Eric Brevig. The Hanna-Barbera cartoon Yogi Bear, will be converted into a 3D project.Joshua Sternin and Jeffrey Ventimilia are writing the screenplay. Not much has been uncovered yet, but its expected to combine live action and CG. No details yet as to what Yogi Bear and Boo Boo will get up to in Jellystone Park.Brevig has a background in visual effects, so it could look very good. The Hollywood Reporter hosts more information; for a debate check out our fourm.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3792</guid></item><item><title>Clue in the works for director Gore Verbinski</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3791</link><description>Gore Verbinski is attached to develop the live-action murder mystery &quot;Clue&quot;. Based on the Hasbro board game, Verbinski will produce alongside Brian Goldner and Bennett Schneir.Jonathan Krauss from Blind Wink called this &quot;a global thriller and transmedia event that uses deductive reasoning as its storytelling engine.&quot;Verbinski will next direct Bioshock for Universal. For more information check out the forum and Variety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3791</guid></item><item><title>Ghostbusters 3 with Harold Ramis, Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd and Ernie Hudson</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3790</link><description>Ghostbusters 3 will be penned early this summer with production set to begin in late fall of 2009. The current understanding is that the old Ghostbusters will appear in the film as mentors, possibly to a new generation. Harold Ramis, Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd and Ernie Hudson are designed to come back according to producers and writers Lee Eisenberg and Gene Stupnitsky. The Boston Globe managed to acquire this information during an interview with Dan Aykroyd. Check out what our members think about this feature; Coming Soon may have more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3790</guid></item><item><title>Fair Game for Naomi Watts</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3789</link><description>Director Doug Liman is set to helm &quot;Fair Game&quot;. Naomi Watts will take the lead role as CIA agent Valerie Plame Wilson. The story revolves around Valerie as her CIA status becomes compromised.Variety has more information, as does our forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3789</guid></item><item><title>Two extended clips from Watchmen</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3788</link><description>Two extended clips from &quot;Watchmen&quot; are now online. The clips feature Rorschach (Jackie Earle Haley). Director Zack Snyder helms the project. View the new clip over at Youtube. This feature explodes into theaters on March 6th. Thank you Coming Soon for the heads up. Join us in the forum for more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3788</guid></item><item><title>The Way Back for director Tom Bezucha</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3787</link><description>Director Tom Bezucha is set to helm the coming of age comedy, &quot;The Way Back&quot;. The feature revolves around a teenage boy who forms an unlikely friendship that gives him the strength to reconnect with his mother and the courage to stand up to his bullying stepfather.Nat Faxon and Jim Rash wrote the script and its considered to be hot property. Shawn Levy, Paul Young and Peter Principato are producing. Shooting will start early next year. For more information check out Variety; for an argument go to our forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3787</guid></item><item><title>Emily Blunt will not be in Iron Man 2</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3786</link><description>Director Jon Favreau claims Emily Blunt will be unavailable for the Iron Man sequel. Blunt will be starring in Gulliver's Travels instead. According to Robert Downey Jr., they are working on &quot;a hot script&quot; to try and get Mickey Rourke to play the villain. Join us in the forum for a debate; visit The Playlist and Coming Soon for more information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3786</guid></item><item><title>Hot Tub Time Machine with John Cusack and Rob Corddry</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3785</link><description>&quot;Hot Tub Time Machine&quot; is set to star John Cusack and Rob Corddry. The comedy, directed by Steve Pink, revolves around a group of frustrated adults. They return to the lodge, where they used to hang out as teenagers to find they are transported back to 1987 via their hot tub.Scripted by Josh Heald, the project is to be produced by John Cusack, Grace Loh and Matt Moore. Shooting will commence on April 20th.This bubbly time machine could become the next Bill and Ted, join us in the forum to talk about it; visit The Hollywood Reporter for more updates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3785</guid></item><item><title>Woody Allen's untitled feature to star Naomi Watts, Josh Brolin and Anthony Hopkins</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3784</link><description>Woody Allen's untitled feature is set to star Naomi Watts, Josh Brolin and Anthony Hopkins. Letty Aronson, Steve Tenenbaum and Jaume Roures will produce. June 19 2009 will see the release of Allen's latest film, &quot;Whatever Works&quot;.For more information visit Variety; for complete and utter non-sense visit our forum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3784</guid></item><item><title>81st Annual Academy Awards show clips from a mass of movies!</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3783</link><description>An array of upcoming 2009 movies was shown during the credits of the 81st Annual Academy Awards. Sherlock Holmes, Funny People, The Taking of Pelham 1 2 3, Public Enemies, Julie&amp;Julia, The Soloist, Up, Fame, Terminator Salvation, (500) Days of Summer, Amelia, Whatever Works, Inglourious Basterds, Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian, Monsters vs. Aliens, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Angels&amp;amp;Demons, Old Dogs, Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs, The Boat That Rocked, An Education, State of Play, Imagine That and G-Force were all displayed on screen by lucky spectators.Youtube is hosting the clip, thank you Coming Soon for the heads up. Join us in the forum to talk about these future features.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3783</guid></item><item><title>Superman Unleashed in the works</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3782</link><description>Legendary Pictures may have &quot;Superman Unleashed&quot; on its upcoming film list according to /Film.&quot;Ramping up the action of its esteemed predecessor, the sequel to 'Superman Returns' promises to raise the stakes and take the audience to heights of action that no other superhero movie can achieve.&quot;There is no mention if Brandon Routh will portray Superman in this one. For more information check out the forum and Coming Soon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3782</guid></item><item><title>Megan Fox is very sexy</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3781</link><description>In an online msn poll, Megan Fox came out on Top of the 5 Sexiest actresses of all time. Halle Berry came out in second place for her role as Storm in the X Men trilogy, with Milla Jovovich's part in The Fifth Element was voted third.Natalie Portman came in at number 4, for Star Wars and Sigourney Weaver was number 5 for her part in the Alien franchise. Fox won the award for her piece in Transformers.Join our forum to decide our own poll, then find out more information at comicbookmovie.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3781</guid></item><item><title>Megan Fox to take over Tomb Raider?</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3780</link><description>Megan Fox could take over the &quot;Tomb Raider&quot; films; that is the latest rumour according to ps3-news. Translation dictates &quot;she'd be the absolutely perfect replacement for Jolie, and there's no doubt guys will pay to see her on the big screen.&quot;Would you welcome the switch over?</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3780</guid></item><item><title>Transformers 2 to star Shia LaBeouf, Megan Fox, Josh Duhamel, Tyrese Gibson, Kevin Dunn, Julie White, John Benjamin Hickey, Ramon Rodriguez, Isabel Lucas and John Turturro</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3779</link><description>Director Michael Bay is set for the &quot;Transformers&quot; sequel. Shia LaBeouf, Megan Fox, Josh Duhamel, Tyrese Gibson, Kevin Dunn, Julie White, John Benjamin Hickey, Ramon Rodriguez, Isabel Lucas and John Turturro are set to star.MTV has a new clip from the action adventure, which is set for a June 24th 2009 release. For more information check out the forum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3779</guid></item><item><title>Inglourious Basterds gets a 3 poster debut by Empire magazine</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3778</link><description>Empire magazine has recently displayed three new posters for &quot;Inglourious Basterds&quot;. Directed by Quentin Tarantino, the war thriller stars Brad Pitt, Diane Kruger, Melanie Laurent, Christoph Waltz, Daniel Bruhl, Eli Roth, Samm Levine, B.J. Novak, Til Schweiger, Gedeon Burkhard, Paul Rust, Michael Bacall, Omar Doom, Sylvester Groth, Julie Dreyfus, Jacky Ido, August Diehl, Martin Wuttke, Richard Sammel, Christian Berkel, Sonke Mohring, Michael Fassbender, Mike Myers, Rod Taylor, Denis Menochet, Cloris Leachman, Maggie Cheung and Samuel L. Jackson.The film launches August 21st 2009. For more information check out our forum, Empire and Coming Soon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3778</guid></item><item><title>Star Trek featurette</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3777</link><description>John Cho, Ben Cross, Bruce Greenwood, Simon Pegg, Chris Pine, Zachary Quinto, Winona Ryder, Zoe Saldana, Karl Urban, Anton Yelchin, Eric Bana and Leonard Nimoy star in the upcoming J.J. Abrams' Star Trek. The feature set to hit theaters on May 8th, has a new featurette from MTV's &quot;Spoilers&quot;. Join our forum and discuss the project now.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3777</guid></item><item><title>Watchmen clips with Malin Akerman and Patrick Wilson</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3776</link><description>&quot;Spoilers&quot; from MTV have aired a new clip from Watchmen. In the clip Silk Spectre (Malin Akerman) and Nite Owl II (Patrick Wilson) resolve a riot occuring at a prison. Be ready for this action packed comic book adventure on March 6th 2009. Zack Snyder directs this feature.Join us in the forum and talk about this feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3776</guid></item><item><title>The Dark Knight makes a billion dollars!</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3775</link><description>The Dark Knight is the fourth film in the world to take more than $1 billion in worldwide box office returns.It joins Titanic, The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King, and Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Mans Chest on the billion dollar profit movie list.Sadly Howard The Duck is not included, but who knows one day DVD sales might push it up!The Dark Knight is number two on list, but with James Camerons Avatar on the way to screens this year, I'm sure the self proclaimed &quot;King of the World&quot; will make sure it doesn't stay that way for long.See Coming Soon for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3775</guid></item><item><title>Jeffrey Dean Morgan is set for The Losers comic book adaption.</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3774</link><description>Jeffrey Dean Morgan is set to topline &quot;The Losers&quot;. Sylvain White is set to direct for Warner Bros. according to Variety.As an adaptation of the comic book, the feature will revolve around a band of black ops commandos who are set up to be killed by their own government. James Vanderbilt has developed the script; which almost sounds like the A-Team. Dark Castle Entertainment is financing the project. Joel Silver, Akiva Goldsman and Kerry Foster are set to produce.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3774</guid></item><item><title>Howl for James Franco</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3773</link><description>James Franco is set for &quot;Howl&quot;. Produced by the upcoming indie company Werc Werk Works the film is set for a March 16th release.The feature will revolve around the trial over Allen Ginsberg's poem; whilst exploring an animated version of the poem itself.Elizabeth Redleaf, Christine Walker, Rob Epstein and Jeffrey Friedman are producing. Epstein and Friedman are set to direct from their own screenplay. Variety has more information on the upcoming feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3773</guid></item><item><title>We Bought a Zoo to be produced by Julie Yorn</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3771</link><description>The rights to memoir by Benjamin Mee, &quot;We Bought a Zoo&quot; have been picked up by 20th Century Fox.Julie Yorn is set to produce. The book tells the story of how the author and his family used their life savings to buy a dilapidated zoo.Having to balance between caring for his wife, who was dying of brain cancer and dealing with escaping endangered animals, this film has the emotional ingredients of a classic.No writer is attached yet to adapt the book. The Hollywood Reporter has more information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3771</guid></item><item><title>Dead Spy Running to be directed by McG</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3772</link><description>Stephen Gaghan will script the adaptation of Dead Spy Running. The novel which has director McG on board is meant to be the first in a trilogy. The feature aims to reinvent the spy genre; exploring the origin story of a trained spy inter mixing the grittiness of The Bourne Identity with the high calibre plot of John Le Carre's oeuvre. McG will direct at least the first film with Jeanne Allgood producing.Jon Stock's book is set to be published in June. The book begins with the protagonist running the London Marathon, where a fellow racer is strapped with explosives. This leads on to a world adventure to clear the name of the man's father. The Hollywood Reporter hosts more information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3772</guid></item><item><title>Terminator Salvation to start Linda Hamilton</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3770</link><description>Terminator Salvation is likely to star Linda Hamilton. Director McG hinted that she will be up for doing a voiceover as Sarah Connor.Hamilton explained that although she has yet to read the script, she is in talks with McG and that she does not know &quot;what direction they will go in.&quot;I'd like to see a holographic representation of Connor to give the next movie justice in the Terminator franchise. MTV has more information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3770</guid></item><item><title>Watchmen clip featuring Jackie Earle Haley!</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3769</link><description>The sixth clip from Watchmen has arrived thanks to Yahoo! Movies. Jackie Earle Haley takes the scene in this one. Directed by Zack Snyder this is likely to be the best comic book movie for 2009.The film will feature the talent of Malin Akerman, Billy Crudup, Matthew Goode, Carla Gugino, Jackie Earle Haley, Jeffrey Dean Morgan and Patrick Wilson.Expect to be amazed when this comes out on March 6th. If you enjoy the clips give our forum members a heads up.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3769</guid></item><item><title>Salt to star Angelina Jolie and Liev Schreiber, directed by Phillip Noyce</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3768</link><description>Liev Schreiber may star opposite Angelina Jolie in the spy thriller called &quot;Salt&quot;. Directed by Phillip Noyce and confirmed by Variety, Lorenzo di Bonaventura and Sunil Perkash are set to produce.According to Moviehole, Chiwetel Ejiofor has also signed up. Revolving around Evelyn Salt. Salt is fingered as a Russian spy and although she eludes capture she struggles to prove someone else is the traitor.Meanwhile her superiors are convinced she is out to assassinate the president. Schreiber is likely to portray Salt's boss and friend.Filming begins next month in New York, but the discussion starts now in the forum.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3768</guid></item><item><title>Guy Ritchie has some pleasing Sherlock Holmes footage</title><link>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3767</link><description>Guy Ritchie was rumoured earlier on this week that he had to reshoot scenes for his upcoming &quot;Sherlock Holmes&quot;. Warner Brothers has denied this; The Sun had suggested that studio executives had been disappointed with early footage, branding one particular scene &quot;ridiculously unrealistic&quot;.Reports now concluded the footage is very pleasing and that Ritchie is scheduled to deliver on time.Robert Downey Jr. stars as a detective; the release date is set this November.Join us in the forum to discuss this piece, for more information read the scoop on Digital Spy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.insomniacmania.com/news_default.php?id=3767</guid></item></channel></rss>